<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mite-Plant Interactions Research Group on The Mite(y) Research Group</title><link>https://www.kliot-lab.xyz/</link><description>Recent content in Mite-Plant Interactions Research Group on The Mite(y) Research Group</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-uk</language><atom:link href="https://www.kliot-lab.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://www.kliot-lab.xyz/contact/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 19:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kliot-lab.xyz/contact/</guid><description>adi.kliot@volcani.agri.gov.il
+972 (0)3 9683093
Derech HaMaccabim 68, Rishon LeTsiyon, 5250
Building 25</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://www.kliot-lab.xyz/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kliot-lab.xyz/projects/</guid><description>Our lab work on mites that are agricultural pests and focuses on several aspect research, primarily related to mite-plant interactions. We use molecular tools such as DNA and RNA isolation and sequencing, confocal microscopy using immunostaining and FISH methods as well as, in the near future, proteomic tools to investigate the various questions we still have about mites from different families. Our current main research topics are:
1. Molecular taxonomy and genetic markers search in various mite families.</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>https://www.kliot-lab.xyz/publications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.kliot-lab.xyz/publications/</guid><description>Adi Kliot, Richard S Johnson, Michael J MacCoss, Svetlana Kontsedalov, Galina Lebedev, Henryk Czosnek, Michelle Heck, Murad Ghanim. A proteomic approach reveals possible molecular mechanisms and roles for endosymbiotic bacteria in begomovirus transmission by whiteflies. Gigascience, 2020.
Martin Tremmel, Hadas Steinitz, Adi Kliot, Ally Harari, Yael Lubin. Dispersal, endosymbiont abundance and fitness-related consequences of inbreeding and outbreeding in a social beetle. Biol. J. Linn. Soc. Lond., 2020.
Adi Kliot, Svetlana Kontsedalov, Galina Lebedev, Henryk Czosnek, Murad Ghanim.</description></item></channel></rss>